Finding Aid for the Herschel Burke Gilbert Papers PASC-M.0268
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Projects, Series 1.
  - The Rifleman, Subseries 70.
    - Lou Scared (cue title), 1962 October 2; 2 pages; 2fl,ob,cl,basscl,contrabasscl,tpt,3tbn,perc, bass; 11 x 17 in; photocopy full score, red,orange,blue,darkblue annotations (Box 66)
      Cue no. 5214. Record no. 1088. 14000's RX recorded in Munich July-August '61. In a file marked Recorded Bridges RX. This cue is in the Library set 3.
    - Lou Scared (cue title), 1962 October 2; 2 pages; 2fl,ob,cl,basscl,contrabasscl,tpt,3tbn,perc, bass; 11 x 17 in; photocopy full score, red,orange,blue,darkblue annotations (Box 67)
    - Lou Scared (cue title), 1 pages; piano short score; 11 x 17 in.; pencil piano short score, autograph (Box 67)
      Cue no. 5214. Record no. 99.
    - Lou Scared (cue title), 1 pages; piano short score; 11 x 17 in.; pencil piano short score, autograph (Box 68)
    - Lou Scared (cue title), 1962 October 2; 2 pages; 2fl,ob,cl,basscl,contrabasscl,tpt,3tbn,perc, bass; 11 x 17 in; photocopy full score, red,orange,blue,dark blue annotations (Box 68)
    - Lou Scared (cue title), 1962 October 2; 2 pages; 2fl,ob,cl,basscl,contrabasscl,tpt,3tbn,perc, bass; 11 x 17 in; photocopy full score, red,orange,blue,darkblue annotations (Box 69)
    - Lou Scared (cue title), 1 pages; piano short score; 11 x 17 in.; pencil piano short score, autograph (Box 69)
    - Lou's Angry March (cue title), 1 pages; piano short score; 11 x 17 in.; piano short score or sketch, 12 staves (Box 67)
      Cue no. 5213. Record no. 98. Pencil manuscript music with red measure numbers.
    - Lou's Angry March (cue title), 1 pages; piano short score; 11 x 17 in.; piano short score or sketch, 12 staves (Box 67)
    - Lou's Angry March (cue title), 1 pages; piano short score; 11 x 17 in.; piano short score or sketch, 12 staves (Box 68)
    - Lou's Angry March (cue title), piano short score (Box 69)
      Cue no. 5213. Record no. 98.
    - Lou's March (cue title), 1962 October 14; 6 pages; 2 fl, ob,2 clar,bsn, 2 tpt, 4 tbn, per, viol, viola (!),cello,bass; 11 x 17 in.; photocopy full score, 23 staves (Box 67)
      Production no. 5200. Cue no. 5213. Record no. 91. Some autograph musical additions in red pencil.
    - Lou's March (cue title), 1962 October 14; 6 pages; 2 fl, ob,2 clar,bsn, 2 tpt, 4 tbn, per, viol, viola (!),cello,bass; 11 x 17 in.; photocopy full score, 23 staves (Box 68)
    - Lou's March (cue title), 1962 October 14; 6 pages; 2 fl, ob,2 clar,bsn, 2 tpt, 4 tbn, per, viol, viola (!),cello,bass; 11 x 17 in.; photocopy full score, 23 staves (Box 69)
    - Lou's Playoff (cue title), 1 pages; piano short score; autograph piano short score, 12 staves (Box 67)
      Cue no. 5215. Record no. 100. Pencil music manuscript.
    - Lou's Playoff (cue title), 1962 October 2; 2 pages; 2fl,ob,cl,basscl,contrabass,cl,tpt,3tbn,perc,bass; 11 x 17 in; photocopy full score, red,orange,blue,darkblue annotations (Box 68)
      Cue no. 5215. Record no. 1089. 14000's RX recorded in Munich July-August '61. In a file marked Recorded Bridges RX. This cue is found in folder Library set 3.
    - Lou's Playoff (cue title), 1 pages; autograph piano short score, 12 staves; pencil music manuscript (Box 68)
      Cue no. 5215. Record no. 100.
    - Lou's Playoff (cue title), 1 pages; autograph piano short score, 12 staves; pencil music manuscript (Box 68)
    - Lou's Playoff (cue title), 1 pages; autograph piano short score, 12 staves; pencil music manuscript (Box 69)
    - Lou's Playoff (cue title), 1962 October 2; 2 pages; 2fl,ob,cl,basscl,contrabass,cl,tpt,3tbn,perc,bass; 11 x 17 in; photocopy full score, red,orange,blue,darkblue annotations (Box 69)
    - Lyric for Laura Lee (Box 281)
      ("Mark's Theme"), lyric by Nancy Crawford, Music by Herschel Burke Gilbert
    - Main Title, 1 pages; 2fl,ob,2cl,bsn,3hn,3tbn,2perc,strings; 11 x 17 in; photocopy of full score (Box 66)
      Cue no. 5201. Record no. 1085.14000's RX recorded in Munich July-August '61. In a file marked Recorded Bridges RX. This cue is found in Library set 3.
    - Main Title, 1 pages; 2fl,ob,2cl,bsn,3hn,3tbn,2perc,strings; 11 x 17 in; photocopy of full score (Box 67)
      Cue no. 5201. Record no. 1085. 14000's RX recorded in Munich July-August '61. In a file marked Recorded Bridges RX. This cue is found in Library set 3.
    - Main Title, 1 pages; 2fl,ob,2cl,bsn,3hn,3tbn,2perc,strings; 11 x 17 in; photocopy of full score (Box 68)
    - Main Title, 1 pages; 2fl,ob,2cl,bsn,3hn,3tbn,2perc,strings; 11 x 17 in; photocopy of full score (Box 69)
    - Mechanical License Agreement unsigned for The Rifleman between Herschel Gilbert and The Benson Company, Inc. (Box 251)
    - Melody Line Sketch, 7 pages; 12 .5 x 9.5 in.; autograph music sketches, 8 staves, 12 staves (Box 67)
      Record no. 24.
    - Melody Line Sketch, 7 pages; 12 .5 x 9.5 in.; autograph music sketches, 8 staves, 12 staves (Box 68)
    - Melody Line Sketch, 7 pages; 12 .5 x 9.5 in.; autograph music sketches, 8 staves, 12 staves (Box 69)
    - Music Catalogues (Box 251)
    - Original Orchestral Parts, 82 pages; orchestral parts for symphonic band; 9.5 x 13 in; manuscript music, 11 staves, 12 staves (Box 67)
      Record no. 26. Orchestrators: Al Davis and Al Polhamus.
    - Original Orchestral Parts, 82 pages; orchestral parts for symphonic band; 9.5 x 13 in; manuscript music, 11 staves, 12 staves (Box 68)
    - Original Orchestral Parts, 82 pages; orchestral parts for symphonic band; 9.5 x 13 in; manuscript music, 11 staves, 12 staves (Box 69)
    - Recording Budgets, Costs of European Venture (Box 281)
    - Recording Costs, 1959 (Box 281)
    - Request by Sparrow Communications Group for synchronization licensing of Theme from The Rifleman, 1994 (Box 251)
    - Royalties (Box 253)
      Statements from Telarc International (Rifleman)
    - Scores for Full Band (Box 260)
      suite consists of two themes (The Rifleman theme and Mark's theme).
    - Theme, 1958; 3 pages; Leadsheet with lyrics; 33 x 24 cm.; Black ink manuscript melody line on 8, 10 and 12 staves (Box 67)
      Studio: Four Star-Sussex Production. Record no. 23. Fountain pen, Herschel's autograph, copyright notice typed. Copyright owner: John Paul Music. Red was pencil through one verse in Herschel's handwriting.
    - Theme, 1958; 3 pages; Leadsheet with lyrics; 33 x 24 cm.; Black ink manuscript melody line on 8, 10 and 12 staves (Box 68)
    - Theme, 1958; 3 pages; Leadsheet with lyrics; 33 x 24 cm.; Black ink manuscript melody line on 8, 10 and 12 staves (Box 69)
    - Timing Sheets (Box 283)
    - Transfer records, The Rifleman (Four Star) (Box 251)
    - Transfer records, The Rifleman (Four Star) (Box 251)
    - Trumpets Onward (cue title), 1 pages; 2 fl,ob,2cl,bsn,2 hns, 3 tpt,3 tbn,tuba,perc,timp,viol,cello,bass; 11 x 17 in.; autograph pencil full score, 24 staves (Box 67)
      Studio: 4 Star. Cue no. RFE 125. Record no. 103.
    - Trumpets Onward (cue title), 1 pages; 2 fl,ob,2cl,bsn,2 hns, 3 tpt,3 tbn,tuba,perc,timp,viol,cello,bass; 11 x 17 in.; autograph pencil full score, 24 staves (Box 68)
    - Trumpets Onward (cue title), 1 pages; 2 fl,ob,2cl,bsn,2 hns, 3 tpt,3 tbn,tuba,perc,timp,viol,cello,bass; 11 x 17 in.; autograph pencil full score, 24 staves (Box 69)
    - Video Mechanical License Agreement between HB Gilbert/John Paul Music & Benson Music Group, 1992 (Box 251)
  - Rin Tin Tin, Subseries 108.
    - Cue Sheets (Box 271)
  - The Ring, Subseries 71.
    - Cue Sheets, Correspondence, 1958 (Box 260)
  - Riot in Cell Block 11, Subseries 72.
    - Mickey Rat (episode title), 1953 December 8; 4 pages; 2fl,2ob,2cl,basscl,bsn,3hn,3tpt,3tbn,tuba,piano,perc,4cello,bass; 9.5 x 13 in; photocopy short score (Box 71)
      Cue no. 14512. Record no. 1214.
    - Piano conductor score, financial papers, cue sheets and correspondence, 1953 (Box 260)
  - The Rogues, Subseries 121.
    - Notebook binder of Recording Logs, 1963-64: Burke's Law, The Rogues (Box 284)
  - Sabre Jet, Subseries 75.
    - Correspondence, Financial Papers, Cue Sheets, 1953 (Box 260)
    - Every Now and then, I'm Too Much in Love (song), 1953; 5 pages; 10 x 14 in; leadsheet, piano score, piano vocal score (Box 75)
      Studio: United Artits. Record no. 1273.
    - Gil Tells Marge (episode title), 1953 July 16; 7 pages; ob,cl,hn,perc,tpt,strings; 10.75 x 13 in; autograph pencil short score,blue,black annotations, 14 staves (Box 75)
      Production no. 9747. Cue no. 7B. Record no. 1234.
    - United Artists Corp. Correspondence, 1956-1967 (Box 270)
  - Sam Whiskey, Subseries 76.
    - Agreements, Cue Sheets, Clippings, Contracts, 1970 (Box 260)
    - Music Recording Logs, Timing Charts, 1969 (Box 264)
    - Music Timings, Cue Sheets, Orchestra Breakdowns, Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 260)
    - Orchestra Breakdowns (Box 259)
    - Photographs, 1968 October 1 (Box 288)
      Photographs proofs from Sam Whiskey Recording Session
    - Sam and Jed Depart (Part 1) (cue title), 1 pages; short score; 12.5 x 15 in.; autograph pencil short score, 12 staves (Box 76)
      Production no. 04902. Cue no. 203. Record no. 1313.
    - Sam and Jed Depart (Part 1) (cue title), 1 pages; short score; 12.5 x 15 in.; autograph pencil short score, 12 staves (Box 77)
    - Sam and Jed Depart (Part 1) (cue title), 1 pages; short score; 12.5 x 15 in.; autograph pencil short score, 12 staves (Box 78)
    - Sam and Jed Depart (Part 1) (cue title), 1 pages; short score; 12.5 x 15 in.; autograph pencil short score, 12 staves (Box 79)
    - Sam Sees Gold (cue title), 1968 September 29; 2 pages; 2fl,2tpt,2tbn,celeste,2perc,3guitar,fender,viola,bass; 11 x 17 in.; manuscript pencil full score, ozalid (Box 76)
      Production no. 04902. Cue no. 700A. Record no. 1299.
    - Sam Sees Gold (cue title), 1968 September 29; 2 pages; 2fl,2tpt,2tbn,celeste,2perc,3guitar,fender,viola,bass; 11 x 17 in.; manuscript pencil full score, ozalid (Box 77)
    - Sam Sees Gold (cue title), 1968 September 29; 2 pages; 2fl,2tpt,2tbn,celeste,2perc,3guitar,fender,viola,bass; 11 x 17 in.; manuscript pencil full score, ozalid (Box 78)
    - Sam Sees Gold (cue title), 1968 September 29; 2 pages; 2fl,2tpt,2tbn,celeste,2perc,3guitar,fender,viola,bass; 11 x 17 in.; manuscript pencil full score, ozalid (Box 79)
    - Sam Whiskey, open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 189)
      Tape Reels: 100-103.
    - Sam Whiskey, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 191)
      Tape Reels: 91-93.
    - Sam Whiskey, open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 191)
      Tape Reels: 94-95.
    - Sam Whiskey, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 192)
      Tape Reels: 88-90.
  - The Scarf, Subseries 77.
    Also known as The Dungeon.
    - Closed Door (cue title), 1 pages; celli; 9.5 x 13 in.; photocopy of orchestral part, 4 copies (Box 130)
      Cue no. 3A. Record no. 1986. Crossed out in red pencil.
    - Corrrespondence (Box 254)
      The Scarf - Includes Summons for the Superior Court in Los Angeles, Music recording breakdown, cue sheets, correspondence including with Marlen Music and budget for The Dungeon
    - End Title, 1 pages; horns; 9.5 x 13.5 in.; photocopy orchestral parts (Box 130)
      Cue no. 10C. Record no. 1991. 3 copies crossed out in red and black pencil.
    - If its Corn They'll Love It (cue title), 11 pages; 1st cl, 2nd cl,piano,violin,bass; 9.5 x 12.5 in.; photocopies of orchestral parts (Box 130)
      Cue no. 5C. Record no. 1989. Corrections in red and black pencil.
    - Insanity (cue title), 1 pages; celli; 9.5 x 12.5 in.; black ink manuscript orchestral part, ozalid (Box 130)
      Cue no. 2A. Record no. 1985.
    - Juke Box Fight (cue title), 28 pages; cl,tenorsax,trombone,piano,viola,bass; 9.5 x 12.5 in.; photocopies orchestral parts (Box 130)
      Cue no. 5D. Record no. 1990. George Fields, copyist.
    - Main Street (cue title), 11 pages; perc, 1st & 3rd trombone,1st & 2nd trumpet,bass,altosax,piano; 9.5 x 12.5 in.; photocopies orchestral parts (Box 130)
      Cue nos. 3E, 5B. Record no. 1987. George Fields copyrist.
    - Silent Pick-Up (cue title), 2 pages; celli, horns; 9.5 x 12.5 in.; black ink orchestral parts, ozalid (Box 130)
      Cue no. 5-A. Record no. 1988.
  - Shamrock Hill, Subseries 81.
    - Assorted Materials (Box 254)
      music breakdown sheets, musicians payroll, orchestra manager's daily report, budgets, costs
  - Skip Taylor: United States Air Force, Subseries 128.
    - Assorted Materials, 1955 (Box 270)
      "Skip Taylor: United States Air Force", final revised shooting script, Stuart Reynolds Productions, with cue sheets, correspondence, agreements
  - Slaughter on Tenth Avenue, Subseries 84.
    - Correspondence (Box 251)
      Letter and interoffice memo re: sound track album of "Slaughter on Tenth Avenue" - Decca Records
    - Financial Papers, 1958, 1964-1965, 1970 (Box 268)
      Decca Records - "Slaughter on Tenth Avenue"
    - Financial Papers, 1958, 1964-1965, 1970 (Box 268)
    - Mum's the Word (cue title), 1957 July 23; 5 pages; 2fl,2ob,2cl,basscl,bsn,4hn,harp,piano,2perc,strings (7,7,2,8,2); 11.25 x 14.5 in; autograph pencil short score, red and blue annotations, 14 staves (Box 81)
      Orchestrator: Gil Grau. Cue no. 2A. Record no. 1356.
  - Stage 57, Subseries 86.
    - Ma Petite, 1952 (Box 253)
      Form of Letter from Publisher to Writer, Assigning Rights Previously Acquired Under an SPA Contract
  - Star in the Wind, Subseries 129.
    - Screenplay (Box 278)
      Star in the Wind by Josef Shaftel In 1948, he covered the War of Independence in Israel and his adventures there became the basis for the best-selling A Star in the Wind (1962) by Robert Nathan. Screenplay includes original black and white photographs taken by Shaftel In Israel.
  - The Theif, Subseries 123.
    - Assorted Materials (Box 254)
      music breakdown sheets, budgets, letters confirming rights, cue sheets, music cue detail
    - Screening Invitation (Box 254)
      invitation to screening and returned screening reservation postcards
  - Three Husbands, Subseries 92.
    - Assorted Materials (Box 254)
      Three Husbands: music recording breakdowns, studio orchestra manager's daily reports, budget, correspondence, financial records, summons for the Superior Court in Los Angeles
    - Orchestral Cue Break Down, 1 pages; 11 x 14 in.; printed form with pencil ms annotations (Box 85)
      Cue nos. 1A-C,2B-C,3A,3BB,3C,4B-C,5A-B,6A,7B-C,8B,8BB. Record no. 1409.
  - The Trials of O'Brien, Subseries 122.
    Television series.
    - Correspondence and Music Budget, 1965 (Box 251)
  - The Vampire, Subseries 93.
    - Contracts and Agreements (Box 289)
    - Cue Sheets (Box 248)
    - Cue Sheets (Box 248)
    - Cue Sheets, 1957 April 18 (Box 248)
    - Sheet Music (Box 288)
      lyric by Alan Bergman and Marilyn Keith, Music by Gerald Fried and Herschel Gilbert
    - United Artists Corp. Correspondence (Box 267)
  - Vice Squad, Subseries 94.
    - Assorted Materials (Box 254)
      Vice Squad: cue sheets, recording breakdowns, studio orchestra manager's daily report, budget and costs, agreements
  - Wanted Dead or Alive, Subseries 95.
    Gilbert was Music Supervisor for the television series for 32 episodes (1959-1960).
    - Wanted Dead or Alive, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 166)
      Tape reel: 825. Log or Cue #2500-2515; digitized.
  - While the City Sleeps, Subseries 99.
    - Assorted Materials (Box 254)
      music recording breakdown, main title list, studio manager's daily report, cue sheets, songwriter's contract between Bourne, Inc. and Herschel Burke Gilbert & Joe Mullendore, agreements, lyrics, script breakdown, correspondence
    - Cue Sheets, 1955 (Box 252)
      R.K.O. Pictures, Inc.
  - Whiskey's Renegades, Subseries 109.
    - Cover letter from HB Gilbert to Herbert Nusbaum & agreement between HBG and Brighton Pictures (Box 251)
    - Shooting Schedule, Script, 1968 April 17 (Box 237)
    - Sound Recording, open reel audio tapes (Box 192)
      Tape reels: 88-90. Film score.
  - Wicked Woman, Subseries 124.
    - Cue Sheets (Box 254)
    - Sound Recording, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 209)
      Tape reel: 1135. Log or Cue #: 8220-8224.
  - The Wind in the Willows, Subseries 101.
    - Recording logs and catalogs, 1969 (Box 263)
  - Without Warning, Subseries 102.
    - Assorted Materials (Box 254)
      Studio orchestra manager's daily report, cast & synopsis, music recording breakdowns, cue sheets
  - Witness to Murder, Subseries 103.
    - Assorted Materials (Box 254)
      Witness to Murder: musician's payroll, studio orchestra manager's daily report, music recording breakdowns, cue sheets, lyric, agreement with Sylvia Fine, contract marked "N.G. Not Used - refused by H.B. Gilbert", agreement, handwritten notes describing scenes
    - handwritten orchestration (number of each instrument) for individual cues on 5 x 7 cards "Vote for Joe Mullendore" (Box 272)
  - The Witch Who Came Out of the Sea, Subseries 104.
    - Assorted Materials (Box 254)
      The Witch Who Came Out of the Sea: recording log, bills, Forms W-4, AFofM contract, notes
    - Witch Who Came Out of the Sea, 1974 January 13; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 208)
      Tape reel: 1587. Log 39 thru 93.
  - Zane Grey Theater, 1960; Subseries 105.
    Television series, 1956-1961. Gilbert was music supervisor for one episode in 1960.
    - Zane Gray, 1959; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 154)
      Tape reel: 785.
- Sound Recordings, Series 2.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: This collection contains both processed and unprocessed audiovisual materials. Audiovisual materials are not currently available for access, unless otherwise noted in a Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note at the file level. All requests to access processed digital materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
  - [Untitled], 1959 December 24; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 147)
    Tape Reel: 773.
  - [Untitled], 1959 September 16; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 147)
    Tape Reel: 774.
  - [Untitled], open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 148)
    Tape Reel: 740.
  - [Untitled], open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 149)
    Tape Reels: 712 and 715.
  - [Untitled], 1965 October 26; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 150)
    Tape Reel: 758.
  - [Untitled], 1964 September 15; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 151)
    Tape reel: 749. Log or Cue # 15640-15669.
  - [Untitled], 1965 October 7; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 152)
    Tape Reel: 751. Log or Cue# 20165-21069.
  - [Untitled], 1962 October 2; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 153)
    Tape Reel: 793. Log or Cue# 11131-11143 and 11076-11082.
  - [Untitled], 1965 October 15; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 153)
    Tape Reel: 852. Log or Cue# 20214-20231.
  - [Untitled], 1964 September 15; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 153)
    Tape reel: 788. Log or cue# 15755-15776.
  - [Untitled], open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 154)
    Tape reels: 789, 790, and 791.
  - [Untitled], 1962 October 4; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 156)
    Tape Reel: 823. Log or Cue# 11146-11164.
  - [Untitled], 1963 May 3; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 156)
    Tape Reel: 1352. Log or Cue# 13217-13251.
  - [Untitled], 1965 September 15; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 157)
    Tape Reel: 830. Log or Cue# SR 35-2186 and 2187.
  - [Untitled], 1963 May 3; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 157)
    Tape Reel: 1351. Log or Cue# 13280-13286.
  - [Untitled], 1965 October 15; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 157)
    Tape Reel: 827. Log or Cue# 20232-20267.
  - [Untitled], 1965 September 16; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 159)
    Tape Reel: 891. Log or Cue# SR35-2186 and 2187.
  - [Untitled], open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 159)
    Tape Reel: 893.
  - [Untitled], 1963 October 7; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 162)
    Tape reel: 896. Log or Cue #13928-13990.
  - [Untitled], 1962 August 16; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 163)
    Tape Reel: 836. Log or Cue# 10414-10433.
  - [Untitled], 1962 September 10; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 163)
    Tape Reels: 837-838. Log or Cue# 10890-10904 and 10825-10860.
  - [Untitled], 1962 September 6; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 164)
    Tape Reel: 840. Log or Cue# 10781-10810.
  - [Untitled], 1962 August 31; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 164)
    Tape Reels: 841-843. Log or Cue# 10758-10778, 10736-10757, and 10699-10735.
  - [Untitled], 1964 June 24; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 164)
    Tape Reel: 845. Log or Cue# 15009-15017.
  - [Untitled], 1962 August 30; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 165)
    Tape Reel: 844. Log or Cue# 10645-10673.
  - [Untitled], open reel audio tapes (Box 166)
    Tape reels: 856-860.
  - [Untitled], 1965 January 5; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 167)
    Tape reels: 861-863. Log or Cue #T3RH-0103.
  - [Untitled] (Box 167)
    Tape reel: 866.
  - [Untitled], 1966 February 16; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 167)
    Tape reel: 866. Log or Cue #T3RH-0509.
  - [Untitled], 1966 August 18; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 168)
    Tape reel: 870. Log or Cue #10-1383.
  - [Untitled], 1964 October 27; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 170)
    Tape Reel: 906. Log or Cue# 16134-16156.
  - [Untitled], open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 170)
    Tape Reel: 902. Log or Cue# 18294.
  - [Untitled], open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 170)
    Tape Reel: 911.
  - [Untitled], 1965 August 20; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 171)
    Tape Reel: 928. Log or Cue# 19187-19187.
  - [Untitled], open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 173)
    Tape Reels: 909-910 and 912.
  - [Untitled], 1964 October 27; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 173)
    Tape Reel: 907. Log or Cue# 16101-16133.
  - [Untitled], 1965 August 20; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 174)
    Tape reels: 880-881. Log or Cue# 119,071 and 19136-19164.
  - [Untitled], 1965 September 15 - 16; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 175)
    Tape reels: 831-832. Log or Cue# SR 35-2186, 2187.
  - [Untitled], open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 176)
    Tape reels: 1114-1116.
  - [Untitled], 1963 May 3 - 1965 September 10; open reel audio tapes (Box 179)
    Tape reels: 1379, 1380, 1382. Log or Cue# 15830-15866, 13252-13277 and 19560-19580.
  - [Untitled], open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 183)
    Tape reel: 270.
  - [Untitled], open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 187)
    Tape reel: 285.
  - [Untitled], open reel audio tape (Box 187)
    Tape reel: 291.
  - [Untitled], open reel audio tape (Box 188)
    Tape reel: 275.
  - [Untitled], open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 188)
    Tape reel: 279.
  - [Untitled], 1961 February 15; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 190)
    Tape Reel: 1124.
  - [Untitled], open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 193)
    Tape Reel: 1368.
  - [Untitled], 1965 February 19; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 193)
    Tape Reel: 1370. Log or Cue# 18031-18035.
  - [Untitled], 1964 September 22; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 193)
    Tape Reel: 1373. Log or Cue# 15889PB-15916PB.
  - [Untitled], 1963 Januray 18 - 1963 February 26; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 195)
    Tape reels: 1093, 1094, 1095, 1096.
  - [Untitled], 1962 December 19 - 1963 January 14; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 196)
    Tape Reels: 1097, 1098, 1099.
  - [Untitled], 1965 February 19; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 197)
    Tape reel: 1337. Log or Cue # 18001 - 18030.
  - [Untitled], 1964 September 16; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 198)
    Tape reels: 1347, 1348. Log or Cue # 15867PB-15888PB, 15777-15829.
  - [Untitled], 1962 October 2 - 1962 October 31; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 199)
    Tape reels: 1285, 1286, 1288, 1289, 1291, 1293, 1294, 1295. Log or Cue # 11030-11063, 11064-11094, 11256-11265, 11366-11383, 10905-10937, 11725-11788, 11641-11673, 11789-11828.